# 大家好 河邊的
Hi everyone! The peaches,
# 桃子
on the riverside,
# 桃子快熟了哦 (註︰因為中英語序不同，把口吃部份換了一下，使口吃更自然)
on the riverside, are almost ripe.
# 哈哈 不要暈掉了
Ha ha! Hope I won't pass out!
# 哎喲
Ayo!
# 哇塞~
Oh gosh~
# 爆啦
It's cracked.
# 好紅啊 這個肉
It's really red inside!
# 專
Exclusive
# 專享 享受的享字怎麼寫 (註︰當然字幕是這樣改了一下，增加觀眾共鳴感)
Exclusive enjoyment. How do you spell "enjoyment"?
# 哎呀 一扭就斷掉啦
Aya! A single twist is enough to break it.
# 你看 那裡有一串芭蕉哦
Look! There's a bunch of plantains.
# 那麼大啦 還沒有人來摘
It's so big now but no one takes it.
# 熟了之後我們就可以過來
When it becomes ripe, we can come here again,
# 在樹上吃
and enjoy on the tree.
# 你看 這顆[SIC]樹 好大呀
Look! This tree, is huge!
# 我上去
Let me climb it.
# 誒呦
Eyo!
# 哇 這個是
Wa! This one,
# 最少有三四十斤 四五十斤
it's a least twenty, or twenty five kilograms.
# 沒味道 現在還沒聞不出味
No smell. There isn't any smell yet.
# 你看 就摘了那麼一點點
Look! We've got just a tiny little bit here.
# 大少啦
It's too few.